{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Bathroom Designers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40210/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40210,"taskName":"Designer - Bathroom","taskDescription":"Design a Bathroom","xmTaskDescriptor":"Bathroom Designers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":53,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Designer Bathroom consultants decorator bath","textMessagingName":"Design Bathrm","rolloverLongDesc":"May or may not have certifications from one or more of the associations that certify experts in bathroom design. Often associated with a firm who will do the actual construction work.","rolloverShortDesc":"Specialist in bathroom layout \u0026 design.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Design a Bathroom.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Bathroom Design \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Hire a Bathroom Designer","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":3,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Bathroom Designer","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Designer - Bathroom","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Bathroom Designer Need","urlName":"Designer-Bathroom","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Bathroom Designers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews \u0026 Cost","searchKeywords":"Designer,consultants,decorator,bath,small,modern","emcCategoryOid":-12019,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Short project description including preferred styles, colors and textures:","primaryQuestionSetId":517,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40210/":{"taskOID":40210,"originalTaskOID":40210,"setID":517,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":626,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your bathroom project? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201936,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Complete remodel","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201937,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial remodel","answerDisplayText":"Partial remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4136,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New bathroom (part of a  home addition or new home construction)","answerDisplayText":"New bathroom (part of a  home addition or new home construction)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":601,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Accommodate disabilities/special needs","answerDisplayText":"Accommodate disabilities/special needs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501434,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Bathroom","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of bathroom will be designed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of bathroom will be designed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3772,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Master bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Master bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2883,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Guest bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Guest bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1374,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Children's bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Children's bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4841,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Powder room","answerDisplayText":"Powder room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501437,"questionDisplayText":"Areas Included","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the areas included in this bathroom design project: ","shortQuestionText":"Select the areas included in this bathroom design project: ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5644,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shower","answerDisplayText":"Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":988,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cabinets / Vanity","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets / Vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1664,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertops","answerDisplayText":"Countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6423,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Toilet","answerDisplayText":"Toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201939,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Sink / Plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Sink / Plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201938,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Lighting / Electric","answerDisplayText":"Lighting / Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2036,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Doors","answerDisplayText":"Doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$10,000 - $30,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000 - $30,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200405,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$30,000 +","answerDisplayText":"$30,000 +","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20655,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1 - 3 months","answerDisplayText":"1 - 3 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200406,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":626,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your bathroom project? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201936,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Complete remodel","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201937,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial remodel","answerDisplayText":"Partial remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4136,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New bathroom (part of a  home addition or new home construction)","answerDisplayText":"New bathroom (part of a  home addition or new home construction)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":601,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Accommodate disabilities/special needs","answerDisplayText":"Accommodate disabilities/special needs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201936,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Complete remodel","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201937,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial remodel","answerDisplayText":"Partial remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4136,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New bathroom (part of a  home addition or new home construction)","answerDisplayText":"New bathroom (part of a  home addition or new home construction)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":601,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Accommodate disabilities/special needs","answerDisplayText":"Accommodate disabilities/special needs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501434,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Bathroom","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of bathroom will be designed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of bathroom will be designed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3772,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Master bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Master bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2883,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Guest bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Guest bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1374,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Children's bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Children's bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4841,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Powder room","answerDisplayText":"Powder room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3772,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Master bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Master bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2883,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Guest bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Guest bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1374,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Children's bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Children's bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4841,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Powder room","answerDisplayText":"Powder room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501437,"questionDisplayText":"Areas Included","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the areas included in this bathroom design project: ","shortQuestionText":"Select the areas included in this bathroom design project: ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5644,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shower","answerDisplayText":"Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":988,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cabinets / Vanity","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets / Vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1664,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertops","answerDisplayText":"Countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6423,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Toilet","answerDisplayText":"Toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201939,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Sink / Plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Sink / Plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201938,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Lighting / Electric","answerDisplayText":"Lighting / Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2036,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Doors","answerDisplayText":"Doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5644,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shower","answerDisplayText":"Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":988,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cabinets / Vanity","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets / Vanity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1664,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertops","answerDisplayText":"Countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6423,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Toilet","answerDisplayText":"Toilet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201939,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Sink / Plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Sink / Plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201938,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Lighting / Electric","answerDisplayText":"Lighting / Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2036,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Doors","answerDisplayText":"Doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$10,000 - $30,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000 - $30,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200405,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$30,000 +","answerDisplayText":"$30,000 +","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$10,000 - $30,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000 - $30,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200405,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$30,000 +","answerDisplayText":"$30,000 +","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20655,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1 - 3 months","answerDisplayText":"1 - 3 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200406,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20655,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1 - 3 months","answerDisplayText":"1 - 3 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200406,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}